Don't worry, it's for you guys only.
Tyagi, these are the people
who decided to be faithful,
not to me,
but to their respective professions.
To be honest,
I didn't become an MLA to fulfil
my father's dream,
I became one to fulfil my own dream.
What is it called?
Power.
What did I ask for, huh?
Just this place, right?
It's impossible to obtain that place,
both legally and illegally,
because that's where Bhaijaan lives.
He can kill for the people
who live there.
And people there can die for him.
Bhaijaan has their blessings.
That's a good thing, Tyagi.
Some are ready to die
and some are ready to kill.
In the future, Bhaijaan
will only feature in their prayers.
Anyways I'll get that place at any cost,
but alas you won't live to see that.
You see, my name is Mahavir,
and I am highly inspired by my name.
Tyagi,
Go.
Damn it.
What have I gotten myself into?
Where is he?
What is his name?
Bhaijaan, right?
Where is he?
Can someone call him for me?
Son, if you call him truly
with all your heart
and he'll surely appear.
Just close your eyes and he'll be here.
If that's what you want.
What have I gotten myself into?
Which one of you is Bhaijaan?
Love.
Ishq.
Moh.
So, now who's next?
- Prem?
- No,
next is someone who's got
nothing to do with 'Prem' (love).
Coming up next is our Bhai,
our beloved brother!
Should we call him?
Yes.
♪ Someone's brother
and someone's lover ♪
♪ Bhaijaan ♪
Right gets right.
Wrong gets wrong.
Because
Indians are very strong,
Vande...
- Mataram! (Glory to Motherland)!
Who parks their car like that, huh?
Oh, he will never
get over his OCD issues.
OCD?
Please don't hurl abuses.
- Obsessive Compulsive Disorder.
- Oh.
Whatever.
Let me introduce myself.
So, thanks to my brothers,
I am known as Bhaijaan.
We are bachelors.
We are not married because
we don't want anyone
to break the bond we brothers share.
Who do you have in your family?
Hmm.
Papa,
Mumma, Wife, and a kid.
Why?
Because the fun of staying
with the family during tough times
is not the same as dying an easy death.
I have a wife
who is 6 months pregnant.
Why do you want to leave her
all alone, huh?
And you, my friend?
Do you have anyone in your life?
My old parents.
You want them to bear the burden
of your death at this age?
You are a bad son.
Hey, handsome.
Who, me?
And who do you have in your life?
No one.
- I'm all alone.
- They left you.
Your expressions prove it.
But why do you want
to leave this world too?
Oh no, I'm done being nice,
now you'll see me fight.
Boom!
Ran away.
This is the first time
I have come across such smart people.
Loyalty is great.
But be loyal
to the faithful,
not to the traitor.
Your MLA
is a scoundrel,
but at least he's not a racist.
Do not come here again.
Goodbye.
One day, I'll kill you and your brothers
right here,
in front of everyone.
Bring it on.
Swag-style Pepsi!
Our Bhai's sexy!
♪ Someone's brother
and someone's lover ♪
♪ Bhaijaan ♪
♪ Dance! Dance! Dance! ♪
♪ We walk with swag, ♪
♪ Our style is rad, ♪
♪ We are celebrating, ♪
♪ Punjabi songs are playing, ♪
♪ We walk with swag, ♪
♪ Our style is rad, ♪
♪ We are celebrating, ♪
♪ Punjabi songs are playing, ♪
♪ My heart wants... ♪
♪ My heart wants
me to dance with you. ♪
♪ Dance! Dance! Dance! ♪
♪ My roar will cause an uproar, ♪
♪ My dance will
shake the dance floor, ♪
♪ My roar will cause an uproar, ♪
♪ My dance will
shake the dance floor, ♪
♪ O' Balle Balle! ♪
♪ O' Balle Balle,
such is the swag of the Punjabis, ♪
♪ They always rock
the dance floor with ease! ♪
♪ Such is the swag
of the Punjabis, ♪
♪ I'll kiss, ♪
♪ I'll hug, ♪
♪ And I'll steal hearts across US,
UK, and Canada, ladies, ♪
♪ I'll kiss, ♪
♪ I'll hug, ♪
♪ And I'll steal hearts across US,
UK, and Canada, ladies,
♪ O' Balle Balle! ♪
♪ O' Balle Balle,
when my friends' drums play, ♪
♪ They make a lot
of noise everywhere, ♪
♪ When my friends'... ♪
♪ When my friends' drums play, ♪
♪ O' Balle Balle! ♪
♪ O' Balle Balle,
you don't stay young forever, ♪
♪ Dance and live your life
to the fullest, brother. ♪
♪ You don't... ♪
♪ Dance and live your life
to the fullest, brother. ♪
♪ You don't stay young forever, ♪
♪ Dance and live your life
to the fullest, brother. ♪
♪ You don't... ♪
You three had made a promise, remember?
That you won't let any
girl enter into your lives?
Had you not decided
not to get married, just like Bhaijaan?
What happened, huh?
What happened now?
Why are you scolding these kids?
They are in love.
They want to get married.
What is wrong with that, huh?
If Bhaijaan doesn't want to get married,
it doesn't mean they shouldn't either.
Right.
- Uncle!
- Love you, uncle!
You are absolutely right, uncle.
You alone understand our pain.
These two are just...
We've had girlfriends
for quite some time now.
We were thinking about telling Bhaijaan.
But how do we tell him?
He is the one who opted
not to get married, right?
- Calm down.
- Easy, easy.
You three are acting like rebels.
How does this make us rebels?
- Right.
- We fell in love.
It's not a mistake.
Everyone has a right
to lead their own lives.
No one can control anyone's life.
Oh, control, huh?
We had no other option.
Who will go tell Bhaijaan that
our girlfriends are not like that, huh?
The honest fact is that
he is our elder brother.
He made a sacrifice.
He performed his duty.
What's the big deal?
Everyone does that for their family.
- Absolutely.
- Enough.
Enough.
Son,
you are crossing the line now.
Honest fact!
The honest fact is that
When you get to know about the truth
you won't be able to hear the truth.
Come on, uncle. Spare us the lecture.
Your brother will never forgive me
for what I am about to tell you now.
But it is time to tell you
who you are,
and who he is.
The truth is that
neither are you three
related to each other
nor is he related to any of you.
Your brother
had met you in the orphanage
where he worked.
He, too, was an orphan.
Then one day, the orphanage caught fire,
and he risked his
life to save your lives.
And the moment he took
the three of you in his arms.
He vowed,
that he would never leave you all.
He didn't get married
because of that vow.
He performed his duty as a brother.
He made a sacrifice
and decided that giving you a good
upbringing would be the aim of his life.
And that was a big deal.
He used to look after you, educate you,
put you to bed and then study,
to make sure that people don't say,
that your brother is an illiterate.
And that you don't feel embarrassed.
Son,
he too will break
if this bond breaks.
No, uncle.
We won't cause him any trouble.
Never.
Sorry.
Good.
But never tell him that you know.
Never, uncle.
Never.
♪ Without you, ♪
♪ I don't want to live. ♪
♪ nothing exits. ♪
♪ Without you, ♪
♪ I don't want to live. ♪
♪ nothing exits. ♪
♪ Without you, ♪
- ♪ I don't want to live. ♪
- Bhaijaan!
♪ Without you, ♪
♪ nothing exits. ♪
♪ My body and soul, ♪
♪ belongs to you, ♪
♪ My devotion belongs to you too, ♪
♪ If you are ever upset with me, ♪
♪ I will cajole you. ♪
♪ Without you, ♪
♪ My life means nothing. ♪
Love you, Bhaijaan.
♪ Without you, ♪
♪ I don't want to live. ♪
Love you, Bhai.
- ♪ Without you, ♪
- Love you, Bhaijaan.
♪ Nothing exits. ♪
♪ Without you, ♪
♪ I don't want to live. ♪
♪ nothing exits. ♪
Greetings.
- Hello, doctor.
- Hello.
We wanted to talk to you.
Love and I...
we love each other a lot.
But I know he loves Bhaijaan
more than he loves me.
If Bhaijaan thinks that
we could impact the bond they share,
then we don't want to do that.
We have a small request.
Please, don't tell Bhaijaan about this.
He will feel very bad.
We've decided to
move out of their lives.
It's for the best that we back off.
- Are you done?
- Hmm.
We don't understand these fancy words.
Tell me what's in your heart.
You know he is my first love!
And you know how difficult
it is to find love?
Our parents will get
us married to someone else.
We'll be forced to stay loyal to them.
And we don't want a second
or third love in our lives.
Right. First and last love.
That's much better.
Now I understand
what you three want.
Your true feelings
have changed my heart.
I swear, it made my stone heart cry.
Next time it'll help remove
the stone in his kidney.
Where are the boys?
Meet our three monkeys.
Homo erect us.
- Huh?
- Homo?
Come on doctor, they have girlfriends.
I don't think so.
They are uneducated.
I don't think so either.
It doesn't matter even if they are.
Both of them are.
But boys,
I don't want you ruining these girls'
lives because you are 'that'.
That's why you need
to confirm right away
that you three love these three girls.
- Hmm. Yes.
- Speak up, boys!
- Yes, we do.
If they are destined
to be in their lives,
then their own brother cannot stop
them from being together.
Bhagya!
Bhaag gaya (Ran away)? Who ran away?
Not Bhaag gaya... Bhagya,
who ran away because of them!
Oh yes!
The doctor has found the cure!
- Bhai's girl...
- So if...
Bhai didn't marry
Bhagya because of them,
then I am sure that Bhagya, too,
didn't get married because of Bhai.
- Really?
- Possible.
But the problem is,
where would we find Bhagya?
- Exactly.
- Mumbai!
Hey, Bhai is here.
Where are they?
I haven't seen them since morning.
- We don't know.
- They aren't even answering their phones.
No, we don't know. No, no.
Bhai, my conscience wouldn't let me lie.
- They went to Mumbai.
- Huh?
Mumbai?
Why Mumbai?
No idea.
To meet Bhagya.
Bhagya.
Hmm.
Who told them?
Forgive them. They made a mistake.
Please forgive them.
We made a mistake, huh?
Ms. Bhagya?
You guys are...?
- We're...
- Well...
You guys are Abhi's friends, right?
Abhi...?
It's your son's engagement party
and you are chitchatting over here?
- Let's go.
- So...
What's wrong?
We think we got the address wrong.
- Yes.
- We should get going now.
Listen...
Moh.
Ishq.
Love.
Come here.
How are you?
We are good.
How is your brother doing?
He is doing well.
- He got married, I hope.
- He didn't.
Can you believe this?
I can believe it.
You three came here to kidnap my wife?
And when you realised that
it's our son's engagement party,
you are making an excuse
that you got the address wrong?
You know they cannot
get married until he does.
- Yes, sir.
- Yes.
- Guys, I like it.
Thank you, sir.
He knows everything.
He's an astronomer or what?
Let's go.
It's my son's engagement party.
We've come here
without informing Bhaijaan.
- He must be worried.
- Yes.
- But...
- We should get going.
- We've some work to do.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Okay.
♪ I love you. ♪
How are you?
I'm good.
What about you?
Why didn't you get married?
The same reason.
Ishq, Moh, Love.
You have raised them well.
Thank you.
Hey, remember, 'no sorry,
no thank you' between friends?
I remember.
Abhi!
- Meet my son, Abhi.
- Hi.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- And my husband, Mr. Him a lay.
- Hi.
- Pleasure meeting you.
He's my buddy,
my friend since 1989.
Since 'Maine Pyaar Kiya'?
It's my favourite film.
I've seen it 50 times.
I know it's my favourite too.
I overheard that you
are still not married.
And you guys are getting me married?
Please talk to them.
I don't want to get married.
I'm having fun.
I'm going to be like him.
You're a bad influence on my son.
No...
But whatever you want,
my son, I'm with you.
I'm with you too.
Now this family reunion calls
for a picture.
Sure.
And smile, please.
Who told them about Bhagya?
- Speak up.
- Calm down or I'll slap you.
And keep your foot down.
Keep it down.
And don't you try to give
me attitude with that cap on!
If you haven't pledged,
I would've chopped your mane right away.
Show us some respect.
We are old enough to be your father.
Hmm. The two of you are, not me.
You are 4 days older than my father.
Don't get into minute details.
The thing is that
they are your brothers,
and they are worried for you.
- That's why we told them.
- Correct.
They worry for you.
They want to see you
get married and have kids.
They want you to have a family.
What is wrong with that?
We were stunned when we learnt
that Bhagya got married.
That she had a kid
and the kid just got engaged.
Oh, really?
- She moved on?
- Long back.
You should thank your stars
that you have such good brothers.
They don't drink or smoke.
They don't have
girlfriends or boyfriends.
They just keep chanting
"Bhaijaan, Bhaijaan" all day long.
So blessed.
I'm so blessed.
God, please help us.
Find us a good sister-in-law.
We three brothers are getting...
- frustrated and desperate to...
- He's God, bro.
He understands Hindi.
- He does?
- Hmm.
Do something, God.
Get us a nice sister-in-law
who is a perfect match for our brother.
- Hear that!
- She needs to be perfect.
I'm sure there's a girl somewhere,
- made just for our Bhaijaan.
- Right.
- Please.
- Give us a sign.
Yes, give us a sign.
Even a small signal will do, God.
Yes, please.
Even a wink would do.
Damn it.
See you soon, Bhagya.
- Bhagya?
- Bye!
Did Jesus really answer their prayers?
Come here, quick.
Lift it up.
What happened?
Thank God.
God should thank you.
Hmm.
Sister!
Sister, you had left your bag out there.
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
Love.
Ishq.
Moh.
Nice names.
I'm Bhagya.
Bhagyalaxmi.
Thank you for the help.
Bro...
God's sign.
Bro,
- we just found our sister-in-law.
- We did.
Where is she going?
Excuse me?
I have rented a house.
Where can I find C-34?
Over there.
Our sister-in-law's a prostit...
Madhu, what was Meena saying, huh?
Call her up.
What is her problem?
I don't know what her problem is.
No, no, no.
Don't get me wrong, guys.
- I just rented a house for a month.
- You are not wrong.
- This place is wrong.
- Right.
- Come with us.
- Yes.
- Come with us, please.
- Please. Come.
Please, come.
So, what brings you here?
I am a conservator restorer.
I've come from Hyderabad
to research antiques.
- Antiques.
- Wow!
So, you're looking
for a place to stay, right?
- Right.
- See how lucky you are!
Our Bhaijaan...
Bhaijaan?
We have a house right opposite our home.
We rent it out.
- I see.
- We'll rent it out to you.
You've hit a jackpot, dear.
Because you'll find my shop
Barakat Antiques right below your house.
You'll be able to do your research
from the comfort of your home.
- Thank you, guys.
- You don't need to thank us.
You can just say that you got lucky.
- You got very lucky.
- Right.
So Mahavir,
what's the update on that place?
You took millions in advance and
promised to transfer that place to us.
But I just learnt that the colony
is protected by some Bhaijaan.
Damn it.
I also heard that all the
people who were working for you,
like the lawyer Ahuja
and builder Khanna...
You killed them all too.
You shouldn't believe
everything you hear.
But...
everything you hear
always has some truth in it.
Don't worry.
Your job will be done.
Tyagi, it's not your cup of it.
Don't bother.
Not my cup of tea, huh?
It's not anyone's cup of tea.
That was a close shave, Tyagi.
It's your turn, boy.
Hello? Yeah, where are you guys?
Actually,
we got caught up with some work.
- Okay.
- But Bhaijaan is home.
- He will give you the keys.
- Okay.
- I'll inform him.
- Is he here?
He is here! He is here!
Bhaijaan is here.
Bhai, we found a tenant.
Someone called
Bhajiya-wajiya or something.
Bhajiya-wajiya?
What kind of a name is that?
How can you rent out the place
to just anybody?
Don't you have any sense?
Bhajiya-wujiya?
What's in a name, anyway?
The name is what matters the most.
Bathroom?
Oh.
I'm Bhagya, by the way.
Huh?
He can't talk or what?
Oh, silent and strong.
Strong!
Thank you.
Hello, Ms. Bhagya. How are you doing?
Just call me Baggy.
My friends call me Baggy.
So Baggy,
tell us about your family.
I don't have a family,
You don't? Meaning?
I have a whole district.
- Oh, district.
- District.
- Would you like to see them?
- Why not?
Show us.
Here you go.
- Here's my family.
- I love it.
You know they call me 15 times a day?
- What?
- It must be quite irritating.
Nah, I love it.
But every second day when they
talk about a new marriage proposal,
then it's a little... irritating.
But my brother, my Annaya,
he is the one who says,
"Bhagya, do as you please."
He's very like women empowerment types.
Really?
Show us what he looks like.
- Here.
- Bro! He's your brother?
I'm sure he can tackle 15 men with ease.
With absolute ease.
You know what happened once?
A lot of rowdies came
to beat up my Annaya.
- And then?
- Then what happened?
And then...
- This okay?
- Mom!
Oh, Swami!
Mom, it looks like
he had another violent dream.
He'll go visit the temple now.
So,
how many times such visits
to the temple does he make in a week?
3-4 times.
He hates violence.
By the way,
what's your Bhaijaan's nature like, hmm?
He looks like the angry type.
No, no. Angry?
He's very soft.
Very gentle.
He's of a quiet nature.
He's very soft and sober.
- Smooth.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
- What happened?
Did a tyre burst?
Not, got to be a cylinder.
No no... it definitely was a blast.
What happened, Bhaijaan?
Nothing. The glass broke.
Ms. Bhagya,
I hope they are not boring you.
No, they were looking
at my family photo.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Why he is not married?
Actually, we're saving
ourselves for the right person.
- Really?
- Yes.
How cute!
Me too.
What the he...
That was a 400-year-old antique!
Thank God. I thought it was new.
Sorry.
Bha... eww.
Yeah.
Bha... bha...
Bhajiye! Fritters!
Yes.
Thank you.
My favourite.
Hmm.
Your stars are not aligned.
I'll give you a book.
You should chant
these mantras every day.
And 1000 times every Tuesday.
What is he doing here?
Wow, he is so handsome.
You are crazy. Let's go.
Let's go, come on.
Bha... eh!
When did you come here?
Have you read the Bhagavad-Gita?
Yah I have read it.
Really?
Rubbish.
[SANSKRIT]
Hey! What the...
Hurry up, or it'll melt.
Oh, sorry ma'am!
He's pissing me off.
If this had happened down south,
I would've...
We people from the south...
From our heart.
When we laugh, we go...
We laugh our hearts out.
And when we get angry, we go...
You want to fight me?
Like this.
And when we get emotional, we go...
What has happened?
Like this.
What about you?
How do you get emotional, huh?
That's it?
And when you get angry?
And when you laugh?
Actually,
I have never had anyone in my life
who made me very angry,
or very happy,
or very emotional.
I'm sure you'll find
someone if you look around.
- ♪ I am in love, in love, in love... ♪
- Is he singing or dying inside?
♪ I am falling in love, ♪
What are you doing, dude?
Sorry.
Bha... eh! Run for your life!
He's gone.
Hey! Come here!
- Good night.
- You...
He ran away.
Well, I wanted to try some of that too.
Can we go hit a local bar?
What is this called... moonshine?
Right?
Let's go.
Can I have a sip?
- No.
- Please.
Here, go for it.
She's going to puke in one sip.
Listen, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Never again.
I don't want to call you Brother.
I cannot even call you Honey.
God help me!
Our Bhaijaan... he's a great cook.
Don't say cook, say Michelin Chef.
- Oh.
- Right.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll try.
Responsibilities and Hardships teach
push you to learn everything
That's so true.
Now I am eager to taste
the food you've cooked.
Huh?
Hmm.
What?
You love it, don't you?
Obviously. It's made
by Bhaijaan, after all.
Right.
I'm sorry, but no.
And you
should try to do better.
Don't get me wrong.
- No, no, no.
- It's... it's not bad,
it's very bad.
We haven't had anything better.
We've been having this for years now.
I'll cook for you guys.
Baggy...
Baggy, I have to say,
both this food and you are great.
Anyone who will marry you
will lead a happy life.
That is true.
Bhaijaan...
don't you agree?
No?
Yes.
Okay then, it's time for dessert.
By the way, what other talents
does your elder brother possess?
He's a very good singer.
Oh, my God!
Just like he was a very good cook?
No, seriously.
- He's a very good singer.
- Really?
What does he sing, huh?
Hymns, Indian classical?
Romantic.
She's laughing?
She's laughing at our faces!
Bhai, please sing a song.
The food was indeed bad.
Go for the c sharp minor scale,
otherwise, your singing
will be as bad as your cooking.
Go for it.
♪ My life had no
purpose without you, ♪
♪ I only started living my life
after I met you, ♪
♪ No matter where you look,
you will find me, ♪
♪ Now we've started meeting
at every juncture too, ♪
♪ I guess I'm falling
in love with you, ♪
♪ I guess I'm falling in love... ♪
♪ I'm falling in love with you, ♪
♪ I guess this is
what you call love, ♪
♪ I guess this is what I've been
always waiting for, ♪
♪ I guess I'm falling in love... ♪
♪ I'm falling in love with you, ♪
♪ I now belong to you, ♪
♪ And nothing belongs to me,
it's true, ♪
♪ From the time I met you, ♪
♪ I have lost my senses too, ♪
♪ Something I have
never said before, ♪
♪ Today, I shall say it to you, ♪
♪ I guess I'm falling
in love with you, ♪
♪ I guess I'm falling in love... ♪
♪ I'm falling in love with you, ♪
♪ I guess this is
what you call love, ♪
♪ I guess this is what
I've been always waiting for, ♪
♪ I guess I'm falling in love... ♪
♪ I'm falling in love with you, ♪
♪ Falling in love with you, ♪
♪ Falling... ♪
♪ Falling in love... ♪
♪ Falling in love with you, ♪
♪ Falling... ♪
♪ I guess I'm falling in love... ♪
♪ I'm falling in love with you, ♪
♪ I guess this is
what you call love, ♪
♪ I guess this is what
I've been always waiting for, ♪
♪ I guess I'm falling in love... ♪
♪ I'm falling in love with you, ♪
Hey, hey, hey!
Why this face?
Chill.
My singing is better than your cooking.
Yeah
♪ I guess this is
what you call love, ♪
♪ I guess this is what
I've been always waiting for, ♪
♪ I guess I'm falling in love... ♪
Wow, this looks nice.
Watch out!
Are you blind?!
Can't you see where you are going?
Stop!
Stop! You don't own this bloody road!
Here we go again.
Hey, what are you doing?!
Someone save that kid!
My son! Someone save my son!
- Catch him!
- Bhagya! Watch out!
Bhaijaan!
You don't own this bloody road!
- Here, take care of him.
- Are you okay, my boy?
- Hey!
- Oh!
What have you two
gotten yourselves into?
- How did you get stuck?
- I see.
- What happened?
- He was driving too fast.
Thank you.
He's gone to the gym...
to work on his chest and legs.
- Wow! Legs!
- Hi.
Hi.
And you are...?
Well, you know Bhaijaan,
the one with the long hair?
Yes.
The one you've been...
We are his brothers' girlfriends.
- Greetings.
- Oh.
I can't believe this.
They never told me.
They haven't told anyone.
Not even Bhaijaan.
They keep telling everyone
that we're "like a sister" to them.
And they have done all
"unlike brotherly" things with us.
Why don't you send over
an elderly family member, hmm?
I'm sure things will work
out once the elders do the talking.
That's what we are here for.
Me? An elder?
What the f...
You have a right.
I'm not going to do it.
Are you guys crazy?
It's not my scene, bro.
It's definitely your scene.
Wait, I'll explain.
Boys!
Look how they're crouching over there!
- Come here.
- They're calling us.
Come here and explain the scene to her.
Come, come.
Rascals.
Tell Bhagya about Bhagya.
Wait, I'll tell her.
You know Bhai had another
Bhagya in his life?
And they loved each other like crazy?
They were going to get married.
Tell her!
Yes, well...
We were kids, so we insisted that we...
Wait, when they were kids,
they didn't want to move to Mumbai.
So, those two had to break
up because of the three of them.
- Thank God.
- They didn't get married because of them,
and now these idiots don't
want to get married because of him.
How do we tell the elder brother that
his younger brothers want to get married?
Especially to a brother
who doesn't want to get married.
What?
Why doesn't he want to get married?
When does he plan to
get married if not now?
Is he mad?
I mean why am I getting so upset?
Anyway, I don't care
if I'm hurling abuses!
Just calm down, bro.
How can he get married?
Everyone here calls him Bhaijaan.
How could he possibly
find a girl to marry him here?
He could...
If he looks around, he certainly could.
By the way, what is his name?
- Tell her.
- Um, Bhai...
Er...
Bhai... his name...?
His name.
- What is his name?
- Bhaijaan?
When we were kids...
- What is his name?
- Actually...
No, actually, the thing is that we
cannot say our elder brother's name aloud.
It's against our culture.
Right, brother Moh?
- Have I ever addressed you as Moh?
- No. Never.
Brother Ishq,
have I ever addressed you as Ishq?
Never, bro. Never.
But why do you want to know his name?
Because she doesn't want
to address him as Bhaijaan.
It's a girl thing.
Oh.
- Hmm.
- It's a girl thing.
But you have to help us.
I could try...
But I don't know guys.
Look, bro, we get it.
We know
how you feel about him.
And you are not doing this for us.
You are doing this for yourself.
Otherwise, it will ruin your scene.
Deal?
Deal done.
I'm Muskaan, by the way.
- Congrats, bro.
- Chahat.
- Congratulations.
- I'm Sukoon.
Bhagyalaxmi Gundamaneni.
Sister-in-law.
Everything is clear now.
For the last 45 minutes,
you've been praising a painting
that is not at all clear.
I'm shocked.
My brothers lied to me.
They didn't lie to you.
They just hid the truth from you.
Same thing, Ms. Bhagya.
And they send you here
to talk on their behalf?
I'm their elder brother
and not some tyrant.
By the way, what problem do you have
if your brothers want to get married?
What problem could I have, Ms. Bhagya?
Oh.
Is that what they told you?
So, you have a problem
with getting married?
Maybe I heard it wrong.
Ms. Bhagya,
99.9% of girls are very good,
but if we are unfortunate enough
to get that 0.1% of girls in our lives,
then they could ruin our lives forever.
But these girls are not like that.
I've met them.
They're very nice,
and they're like
madly in love with each other.
Come on, man.
You should meet them.
Meet them, please.
I'll meet them if you want me to.
I've complete faith in your choices.
I'm sure the girls you guys
have chosen must be one in a million.
Where are your girlfriends?
Meet Chahat, Sukoon and Muskaan.
I can understand why the three of them
fell in love with you.
What I don't understand is,
why would the three of you...
Go...
take your positions.
Go, go, go. Run.
You never know when
Bhai's mood will change.
Well...
Bhaijaan,
she wanted to ask you something.
Go for it.
In private.
- We'll...
- We'll get going.
- Let's get out of here.
- Our fate is set.
Let's go, guys.
Now let's see what Bhagya's
fate has in store for her.
Um, what is your name?
She is asking for his name.
I was called many
names when I was a kid.
"Hey, you!"
"Yo listen!"
"Kiddo!"
"Scoundrel!"
They used to even hurl
abuses to address me.
Then these three were born,
and they started addressing me as Bhai.
How it changed from Bhai
to Bhaijaan,
I don't know.
I've been known as Bhaijaan ever since.
Why?
Um,
would you like if I'd call you Bhaijaan?
Not anymore.
So how about just...
Jaan?
She did it. Let's go.
Bhagya...
Thank you for all this.
Thank you.
♪ Your love... ♪
♪ Has made me hopeless, ♪
♪ Slowly, secretively,
and stealthily, ♪
♪ I always wait for you. ♪
♪ I feel restless without you, ♪
♪ Slowly, secretively,
and stealthily, ♪
♪ I always wait for you. ♪
♪ Slowly, secretively,
and stealthily, ♪
♪ I always wait for you. ♪
♪ I feel restless without you, ♪
♪ Slowly, secretively,
and stealthily, ♪
♪ I always wait for you. ♪
♪ Slowly, secretively,
and stealthily, ♪
♪ I always wait for you. ♪
♪ Your love...
has made me hopeless, ♪
♪ Slowly, secretively,
and stealthily, ♪
♪ I always wait for you. ♪
♪ Slowly, secretively,
and stealthily, ♪
♪ I always wait for you. ♪
♪ Why is my heart
so eager to be with you? ♪
♪ Wherever I look, I see you. ♪
♪ Why do I feel lonely
despite being in a crowd? ♪
♪ Why do I feel close to
you despite being so far away? ♪
♪ I always pray for you. ♪
♪ Whether I say it or not. ♪
♪ I feel restless without you, ♪
♪ Slowly, secretively,
and stealthily, ♪
♪ I always wait for you. ♪
♪ Slowly, secretively,
and stealthily, ♪
♪ I always wait for you. ♪
♪ Your love...
has made me hopeless, ♪
♪ Slowly, secretively,
and stealthily, ♪
♪ I always wait for you. ♪
♪ Slowly, secretively,
and stealthily, ♪
♪ I always wait for you. ♪
What happened?
It happened.
It happened!
Before marriage?!
Love happened!
- Love happened!
- She's in love.
I am in love with your Bhaijaan.
It's strange that
how until a few days ago,
he didn't mean anything to me.
And now he means the world to me.
- Aw!
- So, what's next?
Now, what I just
told the three of you...
Yeah.
I'll need to tell that
to my brother as well.
When?
Right now.
- Right now!
- That's more like it.
Very good.
- Hello, Bhagyamma?
- Hello, Annayya.
How are you?
Okay, I have to tell
you something important.
- Its about a boy
- She found her life partner.
You found your life partner.
Finally.
Annaya, you have me on speaker?
We introduced you to so many boys.
We started to feel that
- you are not normal.
- What are you plotting and planning, huh?
- Amma!
- Bhai, Baggy was saying that...
it happened.
- It happened.
- Come on, kiddo.
He's just like Annaya.
How boring.
What boring!
Forget that.
First, let us see what he looks like.
- One second.
- We've given him a lot of freedom.
- Am may a!
- What's this?
- Such long hair...
- Oh God, it's a girl.
- He's cute.
- So handsome.
He's nice.
Good choice.
He is perfect.
Thank you.
We are celebrating the
Bathukamma festival next week.
Get him. We'll all meet him.
Okay? Bye.
I still haven't asked him.
- Jaan...
- Jaan!
Aww!
We have a huge festival coming up,
Bathukamma.
And Jaan...
Bhaijaan has invited you for the same.
- Nice.
- Bhai...
Please.
Hmm?
Don't worry.
I know they'll like you.
You'll get along well with him.
He's like tall, dark, and handsome.
Very robust like you.
Very daring personality,
but still hasn't hurt an ant,
just like you.
Oh, damn it! Let's go, bro! Run!
Don't worry.
They just scare,
whereas I terrorize.
- Hello?
- Yes, Baggy?
Moh?
Some guys have attacked
your brother inside a metro.
'Next station Phase 2.'
What's wrong?
Bhaijaan is under attack.
We need to reach Phase 2.
'This is Phase 2 Station.'
'Doors will open on the left.'
'Please mind the gap.'
Baggy...
Hey, it's just me.
What is going on?
She's in shock.
No, Bhaijaan.
She's upset.
Why? Because we're still alive?
No, her Annaya,
he's a non violent person.
So, we...
Sorry.
And you are telling me this now?
Why do you guys hide everything from me?
We didn't get a chance, Bhaijaan.
Even if we had told you,
it wouldn't have changed the situation.
Sit.
Please sit.
What have you guys done?!
So much violence.
This isn't violence, Bhagya.
This is called self-defence.
This... this is self-defence?
Hmm.
I didn't know you guys are so violent.
What am I gonna say to Annaya?
What would've your Annaya done
in this situation?
"Come, kill my sister and me."
Would he have said that?
Would he let them beat him up?
Would he let them kill him?
Would he let them hurt you?
- 'This is the last station.'
- Be practical.
- 'Doors will open on the left.'
- Come.
We have reached our stop.
'Please mind the gap.'
- What time is Hyderabad flight is?
- Brother, it's in 3 hour.
How we are going to spent this time?
Baggy is there no, we will figure.
I know what you are doing!
You want me to visualise
Annaya and me in this situation.
But this happened
because you did something wrong.
Your brothers,
these liars, bloody con men,
started our relationship with a lie.
There are three things
that I really hate.
One: What just happened
in there - violence.
Two: Lies.
And Three:
Conmen?
Are you hurling abuses
at me in your head?
I don't abuse, okay?
You want to break up with me?
We could go back in the same metro.
No!
You need to make me a promise.
- No more lies.
- Okay.
And no voile...
- Hey you...!
- Wait, you...!
- Get him!
- Wait, you scoundrel!
What the hell!
You...
'Not again, man.'
This...
this is not as it seems.
I mean, I am not behind this.
It's my bad luck.
I'm always at the wrong
place at the right time.
Then who is behind these attacks?
I am not behind them.
And you are not the target.
Actually, this girl is the target, Bhai.
Mahavir is behind these attacks,
that too
at someone else's behest.
Why would anyone want to hurt me?
He is lying.
He is talking nonsense.
How do you know?
There is just one
man behind these attacks.
Nageshwar Kodathi from Hyderabad.
Nageshwar Kodathi.
Psycho, sadist.
The most renowned goon of Hyderabad.
He makes ministers and businessmen
quiver in their boots.
Anyone who dared to even look
at him the wrong way ended up dead.
Nageshwar and her
brother are archenemies.
He has vowed to kill every
member of his family, one by one.
He first contracted me for the job.
But I didn't want to mess with you.
You shouldn't get into this mess either.
In fact, heed my advice
and stay away from her and her family.
I wouldn't take your advice if you were
the last honest person alive in this world.
Even if not for the
relationship we'd share...
Her being my future wife, mother of my
kids, and him being my brother-in-law...
I would stand by them
for the sake of humanity alone.
If you want us to be kind to you,
then you need to keep
an eye on Nageshwar for us.
The rest is up to you.
I am worried for my family.
But I don't want anything
to happen to you because of me.
So, please go home.
Are you crazy?
Have you lost your mind?
These things sound good only in theory,
and not in reality.
Be practical.
Didn't you see what kind
of a person this Nageshwar is?
And to top this all,
your brother believes in nonviolence.
When a violent man goes
after a non-violent person,
then that non-violent person needs
the support of a very violent person.
Agreed, buy my Annaya...
From today, your Annaya is our Annaya.
You have done your job
by looking after my family.
Now it's time for us
to look after your family.
Indians are very strong,
Vande...
- Mataram! (Glory to Motherland)!
- Yes!
- Yay!
♪ Someone's brother
and someone's lover ♪
♪ Bhaijaan ♪
♪ Lets put rangoli and cow dung (worshipped
as god in south India) in courtyard ♪
♪ Lets put saffron to gateway
and tie mango leaves to the house ♪
♪ With Silver cock's comb
and tanners cassia flowers ♪
♪ Marigold and
chrysanthemum flowers ♪
♪ Lotus and pumpkin flowers ♪
♪ Hibiscus and skyblie
clustervine flowers ♪
♪ Lets make goddess gowri ♪
♪ Lets make every house a festival
of Bathukamma (Life Giver) ♪
♪ Swing O goddess Bathukamma ♪
♪ Swing O goddess
Golden Bathukamma ♪
♪ Swing O goddess Bathukamma ♪
♪ Swing O goddess
Golden Bathukamma ♪
♪ Swing O goddess Bathukamma ♪
♪ Swing O goddess
Golden Bathukamma ♪
♪ Festival of our house
became the festival of our village ♪
♪ The glory of this festival is seen
in the celebration of this Bathukamma ♪
♪ The beauties we see
in our dreams and ♪
♪ The songs we sing
for this Bathukamma festival ♪
♪ Brought spark and
light into our lives ♪
♪ It took me some time to understand,
mate, ♪
♪ as to how our eyes communicate. ♪
♪ I want to tell
so many things and ♪
♪ Want to stay in your heart ♪
♪ Now my heart wants me
to make you mine. ♪
Hi, welcome, welcome...
Hi!
- Glad you made it!
- Hey, hi!
- Thanks for coming.
- Hi!
Hi! You cut your hair?
Once Chhotu got typhoid.
- He was almost dead.
- What?
Almost dead?
- I have read it he was as good as dead.
- Right.
So, Bhai took a pledge
for Chhotu's good health
and chopped off his hair.
Oh.
Today, for the second time in his life,
for your family...
Not 'your family' bro, our family.
Show her the video.
So mean! Don't do that!
- Let him show it.
- Have a look.
Here, have a look.
Oh, my God!
He really likes you.
- Actually, he really loves you.
- Hmm.
From the bottom of his heart.
Annaya,
- my Bhaijaan.
- Huh?
- Baggy...
- Hmm?
Bhai...?
I mean their Bhaijaan.
Yes, our Bhaijaan.
I heard you don't have a name
or a surname?
What do you think of Gundamaneni?
I think it's good.
It suits him.
She is dearest to me.
Take good care of her.
Will do, more than my own life.
We Hyderabadis are very orthodox.
Amma, please.
When we saw your long hair in the video,
we thought you were a girl.
We got scared.
Amma, Amma.
Granny regained consciousness.
What granny got up?
She's my grandma.
She has been in a coma
for the past 8 years.
She regained consciousness today.
Grandma, the doctor has
asked you to take some rest.
Remember her, Amma?
She is your granddaughter, Bhagya.
Yes, she is all grown up now.
So much so, that she has
even chosen her life partner.
Let Grandma rest now.
- Yes.
- Let her sleep.
What let her sleep, huh?
She has been sleeping for 8 years!
She just woke up.
I want to talk to her.
You should leave. You are done here.
I will talk to my mother.
Try our South Indian delicacies.
Pulses.
This is Puri.
Beetroot Khichdi.
You'll surely like it.
You brought joy with you.
Yes.
We believe that...
Good happens when
good peoples are around.
Have some more of it.
It means good people
always bring good luck.
- Right.
- Just wait and see,
your mother will soon start
walking and running as well.
Amma, Nani passed away.
Amma...
What? What happened?
She's gone.
She'll start running, huh?
Good luck? You call this good luck?
They came here and grandma passed away.
Why are you being so negative?
They didn't bring bad luck with them.
Anandini is right.
I, too, am old enough to die now,
and she was my mother.
She lived a full life.
Grandma had been
suffering for many years.
She finally found peace today.
She saw that her family
is happy before died.
She's in a better place.
Yes, Bala.
They didn't bring bad luck.
They brought us good luck.
It's a good thing
that your family thinks like that.
We were scared
that we brought bad luck to your family.
It felt as if we were
doing Nageshwar's job for him.
- No, don't be silly.
- Where is Ishq?
Romancing.
- Bhai.
- Yes?
Nageshwar is planning a big attack
on the Gundamaneni Family this Saturday.
You need to take your call.
Ass!
What's wrong?
Do you miss your grandma?
Hmm.
Nageshwar plans
to send all of you
to her.
This is not funny, Jaan.
Just meet Nageshwar
- and sort this out.
- I will sort it out.
Yes, Mahavir?
The one who saved Bhagya
during the Delhi Metro attack,
and killed your men is in Hyderabad now.
I know him quite well.
He's known as Bhaijaan.
Who are you?
I don't have a name,
but thanks to my brothers,
everyone knows me as Bhaijaan.
I am going to be the son-in-law
of the Gundamaneni family...
I am going to get married to Bhagya.
I'd really like it
if you'd bury the hatchet.
Bury the hatchet?
Do you even know what Balkrishna
Gundamaneni did to us?
I will tell you.
Listen...
My father, Ram Chandra Kodhati
was a god man.
A saint.
Our father and we three brothers...
we were like friends.
For me, he was next to God.
He was engaged in the
business of exporting coffee.
I started using his coffee business
as a front for selling my drugs.
One day, the police managed
to seize my consignment.
And the police officer
who seized them...
I had already greased his palms,
but he got greedy
and asked for more money.
So, I had to kill him.
Balakrishna Gundamaneni
was a respectable man.
That police officer's
family approached him.
I begged Bala, I pleaded to him,
I even apologised,
but Bala didn't do anything.
My father was arrested,
as he was the owner of the company.
Sir! Sir! Sir!
Sir! Sir!
My father couldn't take the humiliation.
Dad,
- And he got a heart attack.
- Dad!!!
Dad!!!
I begged, I pleaded,
but he didn't hear.
My father died because of him.
Your father was a nice man.
It's sad,
that he is no more.
But what's sadder is
that he is no more because of you.
The apple usually doesn't
fall far from the tree.
Your father was such a nice man,
so how did you manage to fall
so far from the tree, huh?
Moreover,
how could you stoop so low?
Basically,
the moral of your story is that
you are a man with no morals.
You think all that you did was right.
You should get some help.
You are not seeking revenge
for your father's hon our.
You have in fact been seeking revenge
for the humiliation you felt.
You have ego, pride, and arrogance.
You're a bad man.
I am no longer interested
in hearing you out.
I have switched myself off.
You are right.
I have ego, pride, and arrogance.
I do.
No matter what people call it,
I call it self-respect.
I like it
when someone bows before me,
begs me,
touches my feet, pleads for mercy,
and begs for his life.
I feel like I am a god.
Yes.
Wait a minute,
you came here to bury the hatchet right?
Do one thing.
Ask Balakrishna to come
and touch my feet,
rub his nose against them
and I shall forgive him.
Now how do I answer that?
You understand what
I said in Hindi, right?
I don't understand your Hindi,
but I understand you.
How can he apologize?
You know he has his own pride.
You know he would rather
die than apologize.
I gave you a choice.
This is not a reality game
show where you'd get options.
You are out of options then.
The only option left is
violence.
Oh shit!
I told Bhagya,
when a violent man like you
goes after a non-violent person,
then that non-violent person needs
the support of a very
violent person like me.
Anna, he will keep talking
and we will remain calm!
Anna, you say okay, I will kill him now.
Anna, ask your Rottweiler
and Pit Bull to zip it.
Anna, we have a problem.
Annaya gave me his surname, Gundamaneni
and before Maneni it is gunda.
Gunda aka goon.
♪ Someone's brother
and someone's lover ♪
♪ BhaiJaan ♪
Interesting character.
Had come here to solve the matter,
but ended up escalating it instead.
- Now my chance.
- No cheating.
No cheating.
I am not getting a six...
you guys are already on the top.
Come on, come on, come on.
Very good.
Oh no.
I've been waiting for you.
What happened?
He's a madman.
He's crazy.
Psychotic.
So now?
Fight it!
Where are my brothers?
They are just keeping a watch.
You turned my brothers into watchmen?
Yes.
They are my watchmen
and you are my bodyguard.
Hello?
Bhai, Nageshwar's men have
reached outside Gundamaneni place.
They are outside.
Doesn't Nageshwar have any enemies?
Any opposite gang member...
Anyone who can take him down.
There was only one man
who could ever stop Nageshwar.
His name was Rowdy Anna.
But he has been missing for a few years.
He was the only one
who could stop Nageshwar.
The only one who could go against him.
Do you know any Rowdy Anna?
No.
Yay!
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Your turn.
- Yay!
- Jaan, I'm getting very scared.
You'll take care of it, right?
Hmm.
Oh no.
What happened?
Going out with my brothers, my family.
Good, family comes first.
Yes! No, no, no. 2-2-2...
What's wrong?
He is the only one
who can go against Nageshwar.
We need to find out who Rowdy Anna is.
Find out about him.
Okay, Bhai.
For Bhagya's happiness
I would accept everything!
The guy's religion, caste,
or class didn't matter.
Whether the guy is an Indian or not,
doesn't matter.
But I just wanted one thing...
I wanted her husband
to be a non-violent person.
I feel sad to see that
my sister decided to spend
her life with such a man.
And you don't blame me for this.
Don't blame me.
Would you get your sister married
to such a man?
Tell me.
Now let me make myself very clear.
Bhagya can marry you if she wants to.
It's her decision to make.
But I will never ever accept you.
Never.
You want to be rowdy, huh?
Nothing good ever
comes out of being Rowdy.
You only lose everything.
Annaya, please listen to me.
They are doing this for us.
They are doing this to save our family.
I faced many attacks in Delhi too.
Who would want to hurt you?
Nageshwar.
Annaya,
if not for them,
we perhaps wouldn't
have been alive today.
Bala, they want to save our lives.
They're just trying to protect us.
Didn't I take care of all
of you after my father passed away?
You did, son.
But they too have done the same thing.
Annaya,
we know that we've hurt you.
We've hurt your feelings.
He is not seeking revenge
for his father's death.
He is trying to satisfy his ego.
He wants to demean you.
He told me that.
He wants you to apologize.
He wants you to beg.
He wants you begging at his feet.
He wants you to rub
your nose against his feet.
And only then will
he leave your family alone.
Is that all?
I am ready to face
humiliation every day,
for my family's sake.
Do not downgrade yourself Bala.
What are you saying?
You will apologise to him?
You will beg him?
Papa! Papa!!!
I am feeling scared.
He's the best son a mother
could have asked for.
He's the best husband
a wife could have asked for.
He's the best father to a child
could have asked for.
He's the best brother a sister
I've never met a man
more principled than him.
Men like him only feature
in storybooks.
This is the first time
I saw one in reality.
We will gladly give
up our lives for him.
With a smile on our faces.
Everyone is in low spirits.
Everyone is scared.
- Jaan, we come from a very simple family.
- I know
We've never witnessed
such things in our lives.
Just imagine what they
must be going through.
This anyway had to come out,
sooner or later.
It's in fact a good thing
it happened sooner rather than later.
But your Annaya's principles...
They are commendable.
And that's a problem, Jaan.
Two people I love,
and both of them are right
in their own way.
Annaya is right and so are you.
If I stay with Annaya people will say,
"Wow, what a woman! She is a goddess!"
"She left the one she loved
for the sake of her brother."
And if I stay with you, people will say,
- "What a bloody witch!"
- Huh?
I mean witch.
And let me tell you one thing.
I cannot lead my life
fearing what people would say,
but these people are
not just any 'people',
they are my family.
The people I love.
I have to choose between you and Annaya.
What do I do?
That's a tough decision,
but I know that you will
take the right decision.
I'll understand.
Oh, God!
On one hand, he is not understanding,
And on the other hand, I have you,
who has a completely different
level of understanding.
You know what? This is all your fault.
If you were a bad man, if you were an ass,
then it would've been
so easy to make a decision.
But you're amazing.
That's the problem.
Why is everything so difficult?
It is not easy because
everything we get easily...
Yes, yes,
I know, it is not valued as much.
It is respected as much, I know.
I know all of that.
I've heard enough lectures on it.
What's going on in
this pretty mind of yours?
What's happening to you?
What's happening?
Well, everything is wrong.
Our geography, our history...
Everything is wrong.
What is wrong?
And how?
Geography...
You... you are from Delhi
while I am from Hyderabad.
And history repeating itself.
You left Bhagya for
the sake of your brothers.
And now this Bhagya is going
to leave you for the sake of her brother.
You know what?
This is that Nageshwar's fault.
I'm going to kill him myself.
I'm going to kill him with my very hands.
Why are you laughing?
I'm going crazy, right?
That's my job.
Do you trust me?
I do trust you, Jaan.
But I don't think Annaya
will ever trust you again.
I trust Jaan.
If there is someone I don't trust
then that's Nageshwar.
That's why I want you to go with Bala.
Okay.
Because Bala is too
nice for his own good.
Everything happens for a reason.
That's why he is here.
He is amazing.
I could hear you in my room.
Idiot.
All of you are still
alive only because of
your mother's good deeds.
Her eyes possess a strange power.
[PRAYERS]
Amma...
You want to know
what I prayed for, don't you?
I prayed for
a change of heart for Nageshwar.
And if that is not possible,
then my son should have a change of heart.
You were in tears.
Couldn't control them.
It's a good quality.
It's a quality for losers.
Loser.
Everyone exploits emotions.
Understanding someone
else's pain is a good quality.
And who would know that better than you?
I don't trust Nageshwar.
Do you trust me?
Do you trust yourself?
Hmm.
It is important that
we have trust on our...
Stick to our beliefs?
Keep faith?
Stay firm?
We trust our trust.
We should trust our trust.
Nice.
Speeding, huh?
Aren't you eager to meet your future wife?
You should...
I will take good care of her.
Hmm.
I will never accept you!
- Huh?
- Never!
Hey!
I accept you, alright.
Come on now.
Bala thinks
I forgave him.
And Bhaijaan thinks
he can save Bala.
They have to be lucky 100 times,
But
I have to be lucky just once.
- Bhagya.
- Shush.
- She just went to sleep.
- Yeah, yeah.
What happened?
Annaya...
you and me?
And that f...
Nageshwar?
Mad.
I am not worried.
You...
That's all! Carefree!
Me. Nothing.
The god up above has all the power!
Vande Mataram! (Glory to Motherland)!
I
Love you.
Jaan,
thank you for all this.
♪ Today, we all are celebrating ♪
♪ Play a peppy tune, ♪
♪ Let the clarinet rule, ♪
Whose calling you, just stop it?
Airplane mode.
♪ Today, we all are celebrating ♪
♪ Play a peppy tune, ♪
♪ Let the clarinet rule, ♪
♪ Let's shake our legs to the music, ♪
♪ Let's sing and groove to the beats, ♪
♪ Today,
we celebrate to the tune of Pungi, ♪
♪ Today, we all are celebrating ♪
♪ Today,
we dance after lifting our Lungi. ♪
♪ Today, we all are celebrating ♪
♪ Today,
we dance after lifting our Lungi. ♪
♪ Today, we all are celebrating ♪
♪ Today,
we dance after lifting our Lungi. ♪
It has been separated.
♪ Let there be a good
around of dance, ♪
♪ Our song will is
sure to cause a trance. ♪
♪ Let there be a good around of dance,
♪
♪ Our song will is
sure to cause a trance. ♪
♪ Mama... mama ♪
♪ Ae mama ye, Ae mama oh ♪
♪ Our dance is very OH? ♪
♪ Do you best, ♪
♪ Today, we all are celebrating ♪
♪ The beat plays, the heat is insane ♪
♪ Dance the summer away, ♪
♪ Play the Pungi, Lift the Lungi, ♪
♪ Tuck it around the waist, ♪
♪ The scene is set, ♪
♪ There is no time to rest, ♪
♪ Today no,
Today, we all are celebrating ♪
♪ Today, Today, we all are celebrating ♪
♪ Play the music loud, ♪
♪ Grooving to the song
we'll have the whole crowd, ♪
♪ Let's shake our legs to the music, ♪
♪ Let's sing and groove to the beats, ♪
♪ Today,
we celebrate to the tune of Pungi, ♪
♪ Today, we all are celebrating ♪
♪ Today,
we dance after lifting our Lungi. ♪
♪ Today, we all are celebrating ♪
♪ Today,
we dance after lifting our Lungi. ♪
♪ Today, we all are celebrating ♪
♪ Today,
we dance after lifting our Lungi. ♪
♪ Today, we all are celebrating ♪
♪ Today,
we dance after lifting our Lungi. ♪
Bhaijaan's getting married
and Ram is getting too excited.
Today, we all are celebrating.
We have 4 couples here
who need to get married.
Please find an auspicious
day for the same.
What are you waiting for, Anna?
If you want, we could kill Balakrishna's
entire family tomorrow itself.
The extraordinary Venus
Period begins after 2 days.
The day after tomorrow will
be appropriate for their weddings.
Do tomorrow's work today.
And do today's work...
Now.
Hmm.
Who are you people?
Why are you coming inside?
I think the family is inside.
We are at Balakrishna's house.
Should we open fire?
Put me on speaker mode!
I...
want to hear them all scream!
Subbu!
Bhagya!
Momma!
Munni!
Bala!
Amma!
Bhagya!
Annaya!
Anandini...
Dad...
Hey, where have you been?
You work too hard.
We work to put food on the table, correct?
Correct.
- Correct.
Well, Annaya.
We'll be able to put the food
on the table only if we work.
Correct?
- Correct.
Huh?
Both my wife and my sister
are siding with him now?
We, brothers, are with you, Annaya.
Brother-in-law, I am on your side.
I see.
- Oh really?
- Please help yourselves.
They open fired at your place.
They thought you all were there.
Nageshwar.
Nobody is here?
Anna, I think the whole family
has left for Delhi?
Phone!
Phone...
Mahavir, the Gundamaneni
family has left Hyderabad.
They are in your city, Delhi.
Your enemy is getting
married to my enemy's sister,
that, too, tomorrow.
Nageshwar,
I guess they don't know
that tomorrow never comes.
Come over.
I'll handle the law and order.
After that, Bhaijaan
and his brothers are mine for the taking.
And Balakrishna's family
is mine!
Be strong.
These things belong to you.
I should have given them to you long back.
And these three letters...
You should read them.
Our bond is stronger than
the one shared by real brothers,
because we chose to be
each other's brothers.
We are brothers out of choice.
Uncle Nadeem had already
told us the truth.
Uncle Nadeem can never
keep a secret, can he?
We should hand him over to Nageshwar.
We could never get
a life better than this.
You have loved us more
than a real brother would, Bhai.
You mean the world to us.
Nothing exists without you.
You guys changed my life for good.
You made my whole life.
What more could I ask for?
So proud of you.
So proud of you guys.
Love you, Bhaijaan.
- Thank you, Bhai.
- Love you, Bhaijaan.
I wish us all a happy marriage.
Yes.
What kind of a person are you?
I am a very lucky person.
You know I like to give hugs
and I don't like to nag.
And that I don't touch
anyone's feet either.
But if I would,
I would certainly touch yours today.
And my dear man,
I am a lucky one, not you,
because I am getting married to you.
And I know you love me.
Too much.
What is it?
It's nothing.
♪ The moon looks fake
when compared to you, ♪
♪ Believe me or not,
that's up to you, ♪
♪ The moon looks fake
when compared to you, ♪
♪ Believe me or not,
that's up to you, ♪
♪ Your catty... ♪
♪ Your catty eyes, ♪
♪ They make boys useless, bae, ♪
♪ They keep following you all day, ♪
♪ Your catty eyes, ♪
♪ They make boys useless, bae, ♪
♪ They keep following you all day, ♪
♪ All day! ♪
♪ Your earrings are mesmerising, ♪
♪ On you, they look great, ♪
♪ When you dance
with your hair open, ♪
♪ I can clap for you all day. ♪
♪ Your earrings are mesmerising, ♪
♪ On you, they look great, ♪
♪ When you dance
with your hair open, ♪
♪ I can clap for you all day. ♪
♪ Help me out, I pray, ♪
♪ Give me your heart, bae, ♪
♪ I promise to do as you say. ♪
♪ Your catty eyes, ♪
♪ They make boys useless, bae, ♪
♪ They keep following you all day, ♪
♪ Your catty eyes, ♪
♪ They make boys useless, bae, ♪
♪ They keep following you all day, ♪
♪ All day! ♪
♪ Shimmering like a true star, ♪
♪ You look so beautiful, ♪
♪ Everyone's crazy about you,
my dear, ♪
♪ You look so beautiful, ♪
♪ Everyone's crazy about you,
my dear, ♪
♪ My dear! ♪
♪ Your tinkling bangles
keep me awake all night, ♪
♪ I keep counting
stars with no respite. ♪
♪ Your tinkling bangles
keep me awake all night, ♪
♪ I keep counting
stars with no respite. ♪
♪ One look is all it took for me, ♪
♪ You have cast a spell on me, ♪
♪ You have cast a spell on me. ♪
♪ I like everything about you, ♪
♪ Your catty eyes, ♪
♪ They make boys useless, bae, ♪
♪ They keep following you all day, ♪
♪ Your catty eyes, ♪
♪ They make boys useless, bae, ♪
♪ They keep following you all day, ♪
♪ All day! ♪
- Jaan!
- Ishq!
You were right, Bhaijaan.
Be loyal to the faithful,
and not to the traitor.
He is a bloody traitor!
Don't spare him!
Dad!
Everyone, go inside!
Bhagya!
Munni!
Go inside, Bhagya.
- Hurry up, doctor.
- Let's go.
Go inside, Bhagya.
- Annaya!
- Bala!
Go inside!
Maaa
O' Goddess,
if you cannot change Nageshwar's heart,
then please change my son
Change my son!
Baggy!
Ishq!
Bhagya...
Bhaijaan!
Baggy!
I said Annaya will take care of it.
What can Annaya possibly do?
Annaya is Rowdy Anna.
Amma, who is Rowdy Anna?
My Bala is Rowdy Anna.
When Bhagya was young,
she got attack by goons.
Seeing his sister's life in danger
a brother took a decision.
He had dropped his
weapons for his sister.
Now he will pick them up for her.
Yogesh!
Come on!
Annaya...
a nonviolent person, huh?
Amma...
Anna...
It's all over.
Rowdy Anna.
What is the use?
You first lost your father.
Then both your brother.
Nothing good ever
comes out of being Rowdy.
You only lose everything.
There is just one last thing
I want to do before I die.
Bhaijaan!
I came to kill them
and you tried to kill me?
They thought you were coming for them.
They are your enemies,
but I am the one you came after, huh?
Nageshwar,
today, you reminded me of my father.
It has become a common fad these days.
Do bad deeds all your life,
and start doing good deeds
just a few days before you die.
Why?
Who do you want to impress, huh?
We have no place up there.
You were right.
Nothing good ever
comes out of being Rowdy.
You only lose everything.
My father was a saint.
He died because of me.
Both my brothers too died because of me.
I should be the one
rubbing my nose before you.
Well, that ends one chapter.
Now let's end the other one as well.
Bhaijaan...
Bhaijaan is gone.
Now this place belongs to me.
Who will stop me now, huh?
Bhaijaan, this is what you call power.
If I knew it would be this easy,
I would have done
this a long time along.
Come on!
Come on, Jaan!
Right for the right
Wrong for the wrong
Blessings have all the power.
Vande... Mataram! (Glory to Motherland)!
I beat him to a pulp.
I crushed all his bones.
Yet, he stands before me.
When my body, heart, and mind say,
"That's enough, Bhai, no more."
I say, "Bring it on!"
Bring it on!
Hit him, Bhai!
♪ Someone's brother
and someone's lover ♪
♪ Bhaijaan ♪
You like cracking your skulls, right?
What is it called...
Brainstorming.
This place,
this locality...
Neither did it belong to your father,
nor does it belong to you!
This place,
this locality,
and this world...
They all belong to the ONE.
And He is not human.
It's not power,
it's willpower.
Understood. Shut up.
I'm done to death.
Game Over!
Chapter Closed!
Knockout!
The end!
♪ Someone's brother
and someone's lover ♪
♪ Bhaijaan ♪
♪ My brother Yo Yo Honey Singh! ♪
♪ Friends,
it's my turn, so come to me now, ♪
♪ I'm so lazy,
make me dance no matter how, ♪
♪ Play the beat and
make some noise, wow. ♪
♪ Sing Twinkle-Twinkle
with me now, ♪
♪ Twinkle-Twinkle, little star, ♪
♪ How I wonder what you are, ♪
♪ Up above the world so high, ♪
♪ Like a diamond in the sky. ♪
♪ Humpty Dumpty sat on a wall. ♪
♪ Humpty Dumpty had a great fall. ♪
♪ All the king's horses
and all the king's men ♪
♪ couldn't put Humpty
together again. ♪
♪ Start the drum roll
let's dance Chottu, Mottu ♪
♪ Jack and Jill went up the hill, ♪
♪ To fetch a pail of water ♪
♪ Jack fell down
and broke his crown, ♪
♪ And Jill came tumbling after! ♪
♪ Mary had a little lamb, ♪
♪ Its fleece was white as snow, ♪
♪ And everywhere
that the Mary went, ♪
♪ The little lamb was sure to go. ♪
♪ Start the drum roll
let's dance Chottu, Mottu ♪
♪ Yo Yo Honey Singh
back in the song! ♪
♪ Friends,
it's my turn, so come to me now, ♪
♪ I'm so lazy,
make me dance no matter how, ♪
♪ Play the beat and
make some noise, wow. ♪
♪ Sing Twinkle-Twinkle
with me now, ♪
♪ How do I dance, you know me, ♪
♪ Your dance moves, just show me, ♪
♪ With this beauty,
I am romancing, ♪
♪ Yo Yo Honey Singh,
I feel like dancing! ♪
♪ Johny, Johny, Yes, papa? ♪
♪ Eating sugar? No, papa. ♪
♪ Telling lies? No, papa. ♪
♪ Open your mouth. Ha ha ha! ♪
♪ Ringa Ringa Roses, ♪
♪ A pocket full of poses, ♪
♪ Husha Busha, ♪
♪ We all fall down! ♪
♪ Start the drum roll
let's dance Chottu, Mottu ♪
♪ Baa, baa, black sheep,
have you any wool? ♪
♪ Yes sir, yes sir,
three bags full. ♪
♪ One for the master,
One for the dame, ♪
♪ And one for the little boy
who lives down the lane! ♪
♪ Start the drum roll
let's dance Chottu, Mottu ♪
♪ Row row row your boat,
gently down the stream. ♪
♪ Merrily, merrily, merrily. ♪
♪ Life is but a dream. ♪